Inventory of the Green Party of California records
Hoover Institution Archives
Green Party of California records
1942-2014
2014C41
Hoover Institution Archives
40 manuscript boxes, 1 card file boxes, 6 oversize boxes, 3 oversize folders (19.6 linear feet)
Platforms, minutes, meeting materials, reports, memoranda, correspondence, bulletins, newsletters, election campaign materials, legal and financial records, printed matter, and audiovisual material relating to political conditions and environmental issues in California. Includes material on other Green organizations at the local, state, national, and international levels.
Green Party of California.
Access
The collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Materials were acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 2014.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Historical note
Following the success in the 1980s of the German environmentally-oriented political party Die Grünen, several American political activists established the Green Committees of Correspondence in 1984. Following this national grassroots movement, several smaller, local organizations began to form, with the first national meeting taking place in 1989 in Eugene, Oregon to develop a national political platform. The California organization was officially founded in 1990, and on January 21st, 1992, the Green Party of California officially qualified for ballot status.
Scope and Contents of Collection
The Green Party of California collection includes institutional records from the organization, along with the personal papers of Danny Moses and Susan King, both political and administrative members of the organization. The institutional records of the party include platform materials, meeting minutes, conference materials, reports, memoranda, correspondence, bulletins, newsletters, election campaign materials, legal and financial records, printed matter, and audiovisual material relating to political conditions and environmental issues in California. The papers of Danny Moses include correspondence, institutional records, notes, press materials, and research materials, as well as materials from his 1994 campaign for Lieutenant Governor of California. The papers of Susan King include institutional records, correspondence, meeting minutes, campaign materials, and strategy notes.
Additionally, this collection contains printed matter, conference materials, and institutional records from Green organizations at the local, state, national, and international levels.
Audiotapes.; California--Politics and government.; Environmental policy--United States.; Green movement; Green movement--United States.; United States--Politics and government--1989-; Video tapes.
- Archives expenses, 2002-2012 (Box-folder 1:1)
- History project, 1999 (Box-folder 1:2)
  Scope and Contents note
  GPCA (Green Party of California).
- In memoriam, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 1:3)
  Programs from memorial services.
- Petra Kelly memorial, 1992 (Box-folder 1:4)
- First Planetary Green Meeting, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 1:5)
- Promotional materials, 1983-2001
  Scope and Contents Note
  Includes printed matter and manifestos for other Green Party-related associations.
  - Green Party of Canada, 1988-1997 (Box-folder 1:6-7)
  - Green Party of Aotearoa - New Zealand, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 1:8)
  - Green Party England 1, 1983-2001 (Box-folder 1:9-10)
  - Green Party of Oxford UK, 1998-2001 (Box-folder 1:11)
  - De Gröna - Swedish party materials, 1996 (Box-folder 1:12)
  - Groenlinks - Netherlands, 1993 (Box-folder 1:13)
  - Die Grünen - German party materials, 1990-1996 (Box-folder 1:14)
  - Die Grünen - Budnis 90, 1996 (Box-folder 1:15)
- Global Greens bulletin, 1993 (Box-folder 1:16)
- Green papers, Green group, 1992 (Box-folder 1:17)
- International working group memorandum, 1992 (Box-folder 1:18)
- Charter of Global Green - Canberra, 2001 (Box-folder 1:19)
- Partido Verde Ecologista de Mexico, 1990s-2000s (Box-folder 1:20)
- Partido ecologista alternativa verde, 2000 (Box-folder 1:21)
- Weaving a Bower Against Endless Night by Derek Wall, 1994 (Box-folder 2:1)
- Promotional materials, 1991-2000
  - Greens in the European Parliament, 1991-2000 (Box-folder 2:2-3)
  - Green East-West Dialog - Europe, 1996 (Box-folder 2:4)
  - Green China, 1992 (Box-folder 2:5)
- Russian Green Party, 1993 (Box-folder 2:6)
- Is California as "Green" as Its Image by Halina Goldchalt, 2009 (Box-folder 2:7)
- Canamex conference, undated (Box-folder 2:8)
- Historical documents, 1992-2001 (Box-folder 2:9)
- Early debate, Spretnak collection, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 2:10)
- Miscellaneous manifestos from other organizations, 1975-2001 (Box-folder 2:11-13)
- Ted Kaczynski's "Unabomber" manifesto, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 2:14)
- Pacifist literature (1940s), 1942-1952 (Box-folder 3:1)
  Toward Security Through Disarmament and Conscripts of Conscience by R. Alfred Hassler.
- Pacifist Research Bureau (1940s), 1943-1945 (Box-folder 3:2-3)
  The Genesis of Pearl Harbor and A Discipline for Non-Violence by Richard B. Gregg, The Balance of Power by Edward Vose Gulick, and Comparative Peace Plans by Theodore Paullin
- Communist Party of the United States, 1995 (Box-folder 3:4)
- Labor Party materials, 1996 (Box-folder 3:5)
- Green Party platforms summaries, 1996-2008 (Box-folder 3:6)
- Miscellaneous, 1990s (Box-folder 3:7)
- Candidate materials, 1992-2013
  - California candidate literature, 1992-2004 (Box-folder 4:1, Box-folder 3:8-10)
  - Ralph Nader, California candidate literature, 2000 (Box-folder 4:2)
  - National candidate literature, 1992-2008 (Box-folder 4:3)
  - Congratulations advertisement, 2010 (Box-folder 4:4)
  - Laura Wells, promotional materials, 2013 (Box-folder 4:5)
  - Roger Donaldson, 1992 (Box-folder 4:6)
  - Sarah Amir Lt. Governor - Dan Hamberg Governor, 1998 (Box-folder 4:7)
  - Rebecca Kaplan - Oakland, 2000 (Box-folder 4:8)
  - Lewellan's Green governor campaign, 1994 (Box-folder 4:9)
  - Mindy Lorenz, Congress, 1998 (Box-folder 4:10)
  - Dona Spring, Berkeley City Council, 1994 (Box-folder 4:11)
  - Andie Book, 16th Assembly, 1999 (Box-folder 4:12)
  - Ross Mirkarimi, 2005 (Box-folder 4:13)
  - Matt Gonzalez for Mayor, 2003 (Box-folder 4:14)
  - Kent Smith, undated (Box-folder 4:15)
  - Danny Moses, Lt. Governor, 1994 (Box-folder 4:16)
  - Peter Camejo and recall, 2004 (Box-folder 4:17)
  - Hank Chapot, 1992-1998 (Box-folder 4:18)
  - Medea Benjamin, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 5:1)
- Green futures (siloists), 1987 (Box-folder 5:2)
- SF Greens, 1985-1992 (Box-folder 5:3)
- Green Consensus, 1987-1999 (Box-folder 5:4-11)
- Explain the Greens literature, undated (Box-folder 5:12)
- Correspondence, 1990-2005 (Box-folder 6:1-4)
- Green Horizon newsletter, 1993-2014 (Box-folder 6:5-8, Box-folder 7:1-2)
- Green Letter newsletter, 1985-1998 (Box-folder 7:3-8)
- Green Party newspaper, 2002-2009 (Box-folder 7:9)
- Green Party press releases, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 8:1)
- Media committee, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 8:2)
- Clippings, 1984-1996 (Box-folder 8:3-7)
- Green Party legal documents, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 8:8)
- Bob Mulholland, 1991 (Box-folder 8:9)
- Sixteen Weeks with European Greens by Mike Feinstein, 1992 (Box-folder 9:1)
- Green Party Tempest by Greg Gerritt, 2005 (Box-folder 9:2)
- Pamphlets, 1987-1997 (Box-folder 9:3)
- Damming the West by Richard L. Berkman, 1973 (Box-folder 9:4)
- Greenpeace Guide to Anti-Environmental Organizations by Carl Deal, 1993 (Box-folder 9:5)
- Ralph's Revolt by Greg Bates, 1990 (Box-folder 9:6)
- Driving Mr. Nader by Linda Martin, 2000 (Box-folder 9:7)
- Against All Odds by John Rensenbrink, 1999 (Box-folder 9:8)
- The Global Greens, 2001 (Box-folder 10:1)
- The Wealth Primary by Jamin B. Raskin, 1994 (Box-folder 10:2)
- What Should I Do if Reverend Billy Is in My Store? by Bill Taken, 2003 (Box-folder 10:3)
- New Greenland by A.R. Eguiguren, 1996 (Box-folder 10:4)
- The Modern Crisis by Murray Bookchin, 1986 (Box-folder 10:5)
- The Green Alternative by Brian Tokar, 1987 (Box-folder 10:6)
- Green Synthesis, Issues 30-36, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 10:7)
- Synthesis/Regeneration, 1992-2000 (Box-folder 11:1-3, Box-folder 10:8)
- Green Politics, 1992-2000 (Box-folder 11:4-5)
- Green Bulletin, 1992-1998 (Box-folder 11:6)
- Charlene Spretnak file, 1985-1992 (Box-folder 11:7-10)
  Includes correspondence, promotional materials, and conference materials.
  - "Greening the West" conference, 1988 (Box-folder 11:7)
  - Papers, 1985-1992 (Box-folder 11:8-9)
  - Committees of Correspondence Amherst Conference, 1985-1991 (Box-folder 11:10)
- Kent Smith file, 1989-2000
  - Security working group, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 12:1)
  - Nader results, 1996 (Box-folder 12:2)
  - International Committee, Green Party US, 1991 (Box-folder 12:3)
  - Costa Rica Verde, undated (Box-folder 12:4)
  - Global Greens, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 12:5)
  - People Magic: How to Manifest the Relationships You Want by Kent Smith, 1999 (Box-folder 12:6)
  - Green Party strategy, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 12:7)
  - Ephemera and notes, 1990s (Box-folder 12:8-10)
  - Campaign, 1992 (Box-folder 13:1)
  - Miscellaneous papers, reports, and correspondence, 1994-2000 (Box-folder 13:2)
- Clippings, 1992-2000 (Box-folder 13:3-4)
- Ralph Nader clippings, 1992-2001 (Box-folder 13:5)
- Clippings, 1994-2001 (Box-folder 13:6-10)
- Clippings, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 14:1-2)
- Membership lists, California, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 14:3-4)
- Green Party California, Coordinating Committee materials, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 14:5-8)
- Analysis, 1990-1997 (Box-folder 15:1-4)
- Green Party bylaws, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 15:5-6)
- Organizing and process materials, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 15:7)
- Candidate results, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 15:8)
- Platform working group, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 15:9)
- California platform, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 16:1-2)
- Platform working group, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 16:3-5)
- Green Party economics circle, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 16:6)
- Platform work - population, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 16:7)
- Platform analysis, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 16:8)
- Campaign and Candidates, Volumes 1-4, 1993 (Box-folder 16:9)
- Women's caucus, 1992 (Box-folder 16:10)
- Santa Cruz state meeting, 1991 (Box-folder 17:1)
- Sacramento state meeting minutes, 1992 (Box-folder 17:2)
- Oakland state meeting, 1992 (Box-folder 17:3)
- Fullerton State meeting, 1992 (Box-folder 17:4)
- Sacramento state meeting minutes, 1993 (Box-folder 17:5)
- Santa Barbara state meeting, 1993 (Box-folder 17:6)
- San Diego state meeting, 1995 (Box-folder 17:7)
- Berkeley state meeting, 1996 (Box-folder 17:8)
- Meeting packets and agenda, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 17:9)
- San Jose/Santa Clara state meeting, 1997 (Box-folder 17:10)
- Steve Saint literature, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 17:11)
- Green Party literature, undated (Box-folder 17:12)
- Sean Stryker, Green politics class literature, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 18:1-2)
- Selected Green bibliography, 1992 (Box-folder 18:3)
- Sean Stryker, Green politics class literature, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 18:4)
- California state meeting packets, agenda, and minutes, 1990-2003 (Box-folder 18:5-9, Box-folder 19:1-2)
- "Greening of the West,", 1988 (Box-folder 19:3)
- Northern California local gatherings, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 19:4)
- "Greening California" meeting in Nevada City, CA, 1990 (Box-folder 19:5)
- Green Parties of the West, 1988-1993 (Box-folder 19:6)
- East Bay Green Party, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 19:7)
- East Bay Green Alliance newsletter, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 19:8)
- East Bay Green Alliance platform, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 19:9)
- East Bay Green Alliance pamphlets, 1988 (Box-folder 19:10)
- Qualifications group, Bay Area voter registration team, 1991 (Box-folder 19:11)
- Alameda County Green voter guide, 1992-2012 (Box-folder 19:12-13, Box-folder 20:1-2)
- Alameda County Green Party bylaws and procedures, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 20:3)
- Oakland Green Party, 1992-2001 (Box-folder 20:4)
- Berkeley loran tree removal, 1998 (Box-folder 20:5)
- Audio Bock - first Green Party candidate in the state government, 1999 (Box-folder 20:6)
- Bay Area Regional Green Party, 1992 (Box-folder 20:7)
- Alameda County Green Party materials, 1993 (Box-folder 20:8)
- Alameda County Green Party minutes, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 20:9-11)
- Alameda County Green Party miscellaneous, 1995-2000 (Box-folder 20:12)
- Alameda County Progressive Alliance, 1996 (Box-folder 20:13)
- San Francisco Greens, 1995 (Box-folder 20:14)
- Bob Vonttoldt, 1989 (Box-folder 21:1)
- Siloists, 1989 (Box-folder 21:2)
- Local California parties, 1988-2005
  - San Francisco Green Party, 1994-2002 (Box-folder 21:3)
  - San Francisco Green Party newsletter, 1995-2002 (Box-folder 21:4)
  - Marin County Green Party, 1990-1996 (Box-folder 21:5)
  - San Diego Green Party, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 21:6)
  - Santa Clara Green Party, 1990-1998 (Box-folder 21:7)
  - Yolo County Greens, 1988 (Box-folder 21:8)
  - San Fernando Green Party, 1993 (Box-folder 21:9)
  - Contra Costa County Green Party, 1997-2002 (Box-folder 21:10)
  - Los Angeles Green Party, 1991-2001 (Box-folder 21:11)
  - Sacramento County Green Party, 1991 (Box-folder 21:12)
  - Nevada County Green Party Alliance, 1991-2005 (Box-folder 21:13)
  - San Luis Obisbo and Santa Barbara Green Party, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 21:14)
  - Humboldt County Green Party, 1991 (Box-folder 21:15)
  - Sonoma County Green Party, 1995-2000 (Box-folder 21:16)
  - Mendocino County, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 21:17)
  - San Mateo County Green Party, 2000 (Box-folder 21:18)
  - Fresno County Green Party, 2000 (Box-folder 21:19)
  - Ocean Beach Green Party, 1991 (Box-folder 21:20)
  - Coastside Green Party, 1992 (Box-folder 21:21)
- Green Party, 1987-1992 (Box-folder 22:1)
- Green Committees of Correspondence, 1985-1992 (Box-folder 22:2)
- Eugene Green gathering, 1989 (Box-folder 22:3-4)
- West Virginia Green gathering, 1991 (Box-folder 22:5-6)
- The Green Program, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 22:7)
- Left Green Notes newsletter, 1990-1995 (Box-folder 22:8)
- Left Green Notes newsletter, Left Green Perspectives, 1995-2000 (Box-folder 23:1-2)
- Green Party USA, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 23:3-6)
- Green Party USA Congress, 1992 (Box-folder 23:7-8)
- Minnesota Green Party, 1992 (Box-folder 24:1)
- Green Party USA program, 1993 (Box-folder 24:2-3)
- Green program committee, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 24:4)
- Green Party USA, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 24:5-9, Box-folder 25:1)
- Green Party USA filing, 1996 (Box-folder 25:2)
- Green Party convention, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 25:3-5)
- Green Party of the Americas, 1991 (Box-folder 25:6)
- Heartland Green politics network, 1992 (Box-folder 25:7)
- New Politics conference, Oakland, 1994 (Box-folder 25:8)
- Green Party in 40 states, 1996 (Box-folder 25:9)
- Green Party Organizing Committee, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 25:10, Box-folder 26:1-2)
- Green Politics Network, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 26:3)
- Green Politics Network membership forms, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 26:4-5)
- Green Politics Network news, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 26:6)
- Association of State Green Parties platform draft, 2000 (Box-folder 26:7)
- Green Party Network, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 26:8-9)
- Association of State Green Parties - Green coordination, 1992 (Box-folder 26:10)
- Association of State Green Parties, 2001 (Box-folder 27:1)
- Green platform, 1996 (Box-folder 27:2)
- Green Party Network, Song of the Frog, 1995-2003 (Box-folder 27:3-11)
- Green Party US platform - official, 2000 (Box-folder 27:12)
- Green gathering, Albuquerque, 1995 (Box-folder 27:13)
- Green gathering, UCLA, 1996 (Box-folder 27:14)
- Washington, D.C. Green Party Network, 1996 (Box-folder 27:15)
- Convention, 2000 (Box-folder 27:16)
- National convention, 2004 (Box-folder 27:17)
- Green Pages, Volumes 1-16, 1997-2012 (Box-folder 28:1-6)
- Campus Greens, 1991-2000 (Box-folder 28:7)
- New Mexico newspaper, 1997 (Box-folder 28:8)
- Hawaii, 1994 (Box-folder 28:9)
- Tampa Bay Greens, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 28:10)
- New Mexico Green Party, 1995 (Box-folder 29:1)
- Alaska Green Party, 1991 (Box-folder 29:2)
- Rhode Island Green Party, 1995 (Box-folder 29:3)
- Jersey Greens journal, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 29:4)
- Institute for Social Ecology, 1987-1998 (Box-folder 29:5)
- Green Party election supplies list, 2001 (Box-folder 29:6)
- Independent progressive politics network, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 29:7)
- The FIJA Activist, 1991 (Box-folder 29:8)
- Randall Toler, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 29:9)
- Miscellaneous materials, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 29:10-11)
- Hank Chapot file
  - Hank Chapot campaign, 1998 (Box-folder 30:1)
  - Opponents, 1995 (Box-folder 30:2)
  - Hank Chapot campaign, 1994-1998 (Box-folder 30:3-7)
- Critical Mass, 1997-2002 (Box-folder 30:8-9)
- Redwood Justice, 2000 (Box-folder 31:1)
- New Orleans Common Ground, 2005 (Box-folder 31:2)
- Genetically modified foods, 1999 (Box-folder 31:3)
- Green Party materials, undated (Box-folder 31:4)
  Includes materials in Spanish.
- Vote, 2001 (Box-folder 31:5)
- Anti-war materials, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 31:6)
- Materials from other organizations, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 31:7)
- Green Party materials for the "None of the Above" vote, 1994-2000 (Box-folder 31:8)
- "Equal Protection and the Wealth Primary," Yale Law Review, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 31:9)
- Danny Moses file, 1984-1994
  - History of the founding of the Green Committees of Correspondence, 1984 (Box-folder 31:10)
  - Committees of Correspondence, 1984-1994 (Box-folder 31:11-12)
  - Green Party of California correspondence and materials, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 32:1)
  - Strategic Policy Approaches in Key Areas (SPAKA), 1987-1989 (Box-folder 32:2)
  - SPAKA fundraising, 1989 (Box-folder 32:3)
  - Early Green Party materials, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 32:4)
  - SPAKA, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 32:5)
  - Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 32:6)
  - San Rafael Northern California Greens regional meeting, 1989 (Box-folder 32:7)
  - Greens in North America report by Per Gahrton, 1990 (Box-folder 32:8)
  - Correspondence and promotional materials, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 32:9, Box-folder 33:1)
  - Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 33:2)
  - Miscellaneous materials, 1990 (Box-folder 33:3)
  - "Greening the West" correspondence, 1988 (Box-folder 33:4)
  - National Green Meeting, Eugene, Oregon, 1989 (Box-folder 33:5)
  - Committees of Correspondence, 1987 (Box-folder 33:6)
  - Midcoast Community Council meeting minutes, 1990 (Box-folder 33:7)
  - Committees of Correspondence meeting agenda, 1989 January (Box-folder 33:8)
  - Committees of Correspondence structure and process, 1990 (Box-folder 33:9)
  - Dee Berry correspondence, 1990 (Box-folder 33:10)
  - Committees of Correspondence meeting minutes, 1990 (Box-folder 33:11)
  - Boulder conference coordinates, 1989 (Box-folder 33:12)
  - Committees of Correspondence Information Bulletin, 1987 June-1990 July (Box-folder 33:13-18, Box 34)
  - Sean Stryker, 1990 (Box-folder 35:1)
  - Roz Mandelcorn, 1990 (Box-folder 35:2)
  - Local Greens, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 35:3)
  - American Green-oriented, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 35:4)
  - Personal Green Committees of Correspondence Archives, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 35:5)
  - Earth Day Wall Street action, 1990 (Box-folder 35:6)
  - Chain letter flyers, originals, 1994 (Box-folder 35:7)
  - Greens documents, 1990 (Box-folder 35:8)
  - PCUS miscellaneous IC, 1990 (Box-folder 35:9)
  - Northern California Regional Greens meeting, 1990 (Box-folder 35:10)
- Susan King file, 1990-2011
  - Draft of "Democracy,", 1990 (Box-folder 35:11)
  - Phone messages, 2001 (Box-folder 35:12)
  - Contact lists, 2004 (Box-folder 36:1)
  - Direct mail, 2000 (Box-folder 36:2)
  - Coordinating meeting minutes, 2001 (Box-folder 36:3)
  - Meeting minutes, 2001 (Box-folder 36:4)
  - Sign in sheet, 2001 (Box-folder 36:5)
  - Election information, 2002 (Box-folder 36:6)
  - Green Party campaigns, 2003 (Box-folder 36:7)
  - San Francisco Green Party, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 36:8)
  - State meeting, 2004 (Box-folder 36:9)
  - Caravan contacts, 2005 (Box-folder 36:10)
  - Green Transportation Justice Working Group, 2001 (Box-folder 36:11)
  - Candidate archive lists, undated (Box-folder 36:12)
  - World Environment Day, 2005 (Box-folder 36:13)
  - March meeting, 2004 (Box-folder 36:14)
  - Green Voice, 2011 (Box-folder 36:15)
  - Notes, 2003-2007 (Box-folder 36:16-17)
  - Contacts, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 36:18)
  - Minimum wage campaign, 2004 (Box-folder 36:19)
  - General Green meeting minutes, 2002 (Box-folder 36:20)
  - Press release, 2005 (Box-folder 36:21)
  - San Francisco Green Party notes, 2003 (Box-folder 37:1)
  - Meeting notes, undated (Box-folder 37:2)
  - Master copies candidate flyers, undated (Box-folder 37:3)
  - San Francisco Green Party, 2004 (Box-folder 37:4)
  - San Francisco Green Party Working Group, 2004 (Box-folder 37:5)
  - San Francisco Green Party letterhead, 2000s (Box-folder 37:6)
  - MVD notes, undated (Box-folder 37:7)
  - Proposition J, 2005 (Box-folder 37:8)
  - Campaign and Issues Working Group, 2005 (Box-folder 37:9)
  - Krissy for Congress, 2006 (Box-folder 37:10)
  - Office working group, 2000s (Box-folder 37:11)
  - Working group notes, 2000s (Box-folder 37:12)
  - San Francisco training, 2002 (Box-folder 37:13)
  - San Francisco Greens flyers, 1999-2005 (Box-folder 37:14)
  - San Francisco Green Party sign in sheets, 2004 (Box-folder 37:15)
  - Krissy Keefer for Congress staff meeting, 2006 (Box-folder 37:16)
  - Field plan, 2006 (Box-folder 37:17)
  - San Francisco post-election party, 2006 (Box-folder 37:18)
  - San Francisco campaign literature, 2006 (Box-folder 37:19)
  - Clean elections, 2002 (Box-folder 37:20)
  - Business cards, undated (Box-folder 37:21)
  - Pacific Northwest Campaign School, 2003 (Box-folder 38:1)
  - Miscellaneous, 2001 (Box-folder 38:2)
  - Susan King campaign, 2004 (Box-folder 38:3)
  - Renee Saucedo campaign (Box-folder 38:4)
  - Prospects, 2003 (Box-folder 38:5)
  - Aimee Anderson campaign strategy and planning, 2006 (Box-folder 38:6)
  - Terry Brown campaign, 2004 (Box-folder 38:7)
  - Aimee Anderson campaign, 2006 (Box-folder 38:8)
  - Demographics, 2006 (Box-folder 38:9)
  - Endorsements, 2006 (Box-folder 38:10)
  - Ethics Committee, 2004 (Box-folder 38:11)
  - Aimee Anderson New Plan, 2006 (Box-folder 38:12)
  - List leads, 2000 (Box-folder 38:13)
  - World Environment Day, 2005 (Box-folder 38:14)
  - San Francisco Green Party notes, 2002 (Box-folder 38:15)
  - Transportation Committee information, 2000s (Box-folder 38:16)
  - Campaign Training Working Group, 2000s (Box-folder 38:17)
  - Event flyers, 2005 (Box-folder 38:18)
  - California Green Party, 2002 (Box-folder 38:19)
  - Line item report, 2002 (Box-folder 38:20)
  - Campaign training, 2002 (Box-folder 39:1)
  - Fur ban materials, 2001 (Box-folder 39:2)
  - Super rally meetings, 2000 (Box-folder 39:3)
  - Hamburg list, 2000s (Box-folder 39:4)
  - Krissy Keefer flyers, 2006 (Box-folder 39:5)
  - San Francisco Green Party, 2003 (Box-folder 39:6)
  - Event flyers, 2004 (Box-folder 39:7)
  - Krissy Keefer meeting notes, 2006 (Box-folder 39:8)
  - Hayes Valley Neighborhood Association, 2004 (Box-folder 39:9)
  - Voting ballot initiatives, gun ban, 2004 (Box-folder 39:10)
  - Matt Gonzalez campaign, 2000s (Box-folder 39:11)